You could even win a reward!
Hello there!
So yummy!
It somehow tastes even better in the heat.
I just love seeing the happy
faces of my satisfied customers.
Numbing ice cream on a
hot day is non-negotiable.
Though I'll admit that frozen
fruit was pretty tasty too.
I've never vended frozen fruit.
You heard right, Boxo.
See, Kiko, you're selling it.
Of course, my pleasure.
Here you go. Oh, yeah!
So shiny!
I hope you enjoy it.
Dastardly.
I should have expected no
less from my business rival.
What a sweet kiddo.
Although, I guess she's technically
a full-fledged adult now.
I think she's even better at freezing
stuff now that she's officially a woman.
So she's freezing fresh fruit
and then selling it as a dessert.
That's a rock-solid business.
For sure, and those grep
things were especially tasty!
Ooh, and I'll have to give them a try!
Now that Temptress is
trying to steal my partner?
If you're looking for a food
war, consider me enlisted!
On the outside, I'm just a big metal boss,
but inside, I've still got a human soul!
In this new world of wonders,
I travel to and fro on the back
of my super strong partner, LAMAS!
The name is Boxxo. Hello there!
That means yes, by the way.
I'll see you guys later
Don't you see me?
You'll be my favorite.
Take it take it.
I'm going to walk you through the sea.
I'm going to go to the moon.
I'll go to the moon.
That's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to be the only one
that I'm going to be with you.
I'm not going to end it!
Fiend, I saw that smug grin
disguised as an innocent smile.
I can't wait to wipe that look off your
face with the power of quality vending.
I must answer the call of food service.
I even begged, I mean, asked
Lamas and Mishuel to help.
Um, hey everyone,
we're selling extra creamy ice cream
today and there's plenty to go around.
And today only, we're offering our
high-quality ice cream at low-quality prices.
It was a worthy rivalry
while it lasted, but too bad.
No mere mortal can measure up
to the power of my vending.
For some reason,
the next day, there was a huge crowd
champing at the bit for cold fruit.
Come on, come on.
We've got yummy frozen fruit over here.
It's so delicious.
You should treat yourself.
Fresh reinforcements from
the clear flow lake stratum.
She even used food to
recruit the gluttons.
Guess it's time to vend
out the big guns, baby.
Now that's how you kill the competition.
Victory shall be mine.
Our bitter sales battle waged on for four
whole days and ended in a surprise attack.
We thanked our friends for
their help with a nice meal.
Shwee and the band of
gluttons took full advantage.
They got the priciest things on the menu,
eating through our revenue and then some.
Thus, the war of the frozen snacks
ended in mutual defeat. The losers!
Since our work was more
than finished there,
we decided to mosey on back to
the clear flow lake stratum.
Good work.
We really owe you one.
Thanks for everything.
That's weird.
Seems like something's weighing on her.
Ah, there's no place like home.
I was starting to miss
this rectangle of dirt.
Hey, Boxo, go ahead and give me the usual.
Your drinks invigorate me to my very core.
Thank you very much.
We've been back a few days now.
Fall will be here soon.
It's wild.
I've been here for almost a full year.
Time truly does fly.
For the last few days, I
haven't seen Lamas or Hulemy.
They must be busy or something.
It's a bit lonely.
Hey, Voxo! Lamas?
I've been crazy busy and
totally neglecting you.
Give me a chance to make it right
with some late-night bonding, okay?
Hello there!
No man, flesh, or steel could refuse
Lamas when she's serving that look.
I'm whipped!
And loving it. Yay!
Let's get cozy in my tent.
Huh? What gives?
Cheers to you!
Wishing you a happy birthday, Boxo!
Wait, is it my birthday?
To be fair, I don't
know when you were born,
but it's creeping up on a year
since we first crossed paths?
so I thought it was as good a time
as any to celebrate your existence.
Hopefully that's okay with you.
I'm so darn happy and surprised right now.
I don't know how to react.
It's a good thing I can't ugly cry
or I might have short-circuited.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
And Kikuyu, we all want to say
happy birthday to you, too.
Oh, wow.
That's sweet of you.
Oh, yeah.
Kikuyu's birthday wasn't too long ago.
It's a double birthday bash.
That's twice as nice.
thanks boxer we owe you true without
your assistance the origin stratum
would be a pile of rubble we all wanted
to give you a proper thanks you're
a real hero as far as we're concerned
them's facts we owe you one i come
bearing an official certificate of
recognition from the Hunter Association.
Oh, you've earned it.
Dead!
I've been racking my brain
thinking of the best gift.
This is what I came up with,
so I really hope you like it.
I enhanced the elasticity
of the stabilizer ropes.
Now it can handle unexpected
transformations with ease.
That's awesome sauce!
Now I can change my look on
the fly without worrying.
I guess I'm the last
one to gift you up, huh?
Bet you're curious what I got ya.
It's a cake!
That book you gave me had
all kinds of party pictures.
That's where I came up with the
inspiration to make you a birthday cake.
So, um, was it a good surprise?
Yes, thank you.
I'm easily the luckiest vending
machine in the entire universe!
I got a birthday cake in another world!
If vending machines could cry, everyone
here would be drowning about now!
And this one's for Kikuyu!
It's so pretty!
The candles are waiting!
Go ahead and blow them out!
Happy birthday, Boxxo and Kikuyu!
How lovely!
Dorn!
I don't know how to process this!
I did not have turn into
a vending machine and have
lots of friends celebrate my
birthday on my bingo card!
The phone tonight is something special.
Too bad the grandkids aren't
here to enjoy it with us.
I'm tempted to take some home
and dine on it tomorrow, too.
And this wine is delightfully smooth
with just a slight hint of sweetness.
I deserve to have a super fun
and special drink tonight, too!
Of course, we secured this
fizzy-fruity one just for you.
Everyone talked up how much
they were loving the feast,
but I came to regret
busting out the booze.
Pull yourself together, man.
Oh, hey, Boxo.
I got an awesome new
invention all invented.
You gotta check it out
sometime, all right?
Hey, you're not taking me seriously,
I can tell, so you got to thank it.
How you doing, Boxo? Are you happy?
I hope the answer is
hello there, because I am.
I love feeling your cold
steel against my warm skin.
Are you having fun yet?
Because I'm having an
absolute blast, you know.
You're blasted, all right.
I'm having fun, too.
More than you could know.
Hello there.
Here and that's a huge load off.
I was worried this whole time?
That maybe you're just being nice.
and I'm actually a big
stinkin' bother to you.
Boxo buddy, wanna know something?
Hello there.
If I had a wish, it would be to stay
right by your side forever and ever.
Hello there.
I pour my heart out and all
you can say is hello there?
Fine, if I had a second wish,
it would be for you to talk.
Aw, she's too freakin'
adorable as a sloppy drunk.
That girl's got my number.
All right, time to show off.
You are cute when you dare ink.
Boxxo!
I need to speak with you about something.
Do you have time tonight?
Something has clearly been
bugging her the last few days.
Is she ready to share?
Hello there!
Sorry for the late hour.
The truth is, we think the time has
come for us to leave the dungeon.
I thought that might be it.
I hate leaving it all behind when this
place is still plagued by odd occurrences.
I know it's awfully selfish.
You're not selfish. You've helped a ton.
I've got no complaints here.
Blossoming into an adult
has increased my power.
I find that I can now hear the
piece of Field speaking to me.
I think returning Field to their
main body could bring them back.
I must try, and thankfully I can rely on
Field's powers to open up the path for me.
She's going all out to meet the
dude who reincarnated as a Field.
You do you, girl.
You're sure it's okay for me to go?
Hello there!
It just occurred to me
this might be the last
time we talk you know
the Nether Lord's power
isn't enough not to get you two out of the
dungeon please tell me you
have a plan I'll open a
temporary path by
channeling my magic into a
transfer circle Hula Me's
theory but there's no
guarantee and it's risky
she's very much against
the idea since it's quite
dangerous and may not work.
Not gonna lie, Geolami brings points.
I'm well aware of that!
but I have to find Field, and I
won't give up the search until I do!
He's that important to you?
You're legitimately willing to
risk your life for this guy?
Yes.
And for the children, too.
I have enough magic power to share.
So it's time.
I know I must leave this place now.
But your smiling faces...
It made me lose my resolve.
Wipe those tears away. It's fine.
You are saving someone you care about.
Jenna!
Walk away knowing you did a swell job.
It's a huge ensemble,
so we'll be just fine.
Really, you've done a lot for us.
We've had a heck of a time together.
I'm grateful.
Yes, so am I.
I'll cherish these memories.
It's been fun.
Goodbye.
At least for now.
We'll meet again, and I can't
wait until that day comes, Kikuyu.
I look forward to serving you again.
The next morning, I gave everyone
the letters Kikuyu had left for them.
Whoever that person is, I
hope she's able to meet him.
I agree.
If there's even the slightest chance it
will work, she has to give it a shot!
Or she'll regret it for
the rest of her life.
It feels kind of lonely without her.
Hello there.
Alright, what's our plan of attack?
The dog mountain stratum and the
everlasting stratum are all that remain.
I assume we'll want to bolster
our forces before we go!
Yeesh, kiko yu's shoes are
going to be really hard to fill?
Indeed, it's pivotal, and I'm afraid I
can't spare anyone else for this task.
As expected, I'm thinking I'll invite
someone from the Menagerie of Fools.
Have you lost it?
The fool I have in mind
is talented and has
certain abilities that our
lineup is sorely lacking,
personality aside.
Yeah, can't argue on the talent front.
It's def-legit, despite that temperament.
Should we be concerned
that they both think
our next edition kind
of sucks as a person?
We need all the help we can get.
Any idea where we can find him?
Though I can't say for
sure, I have a hunch.
And it will require travel
to a new stratum. Gotcha.
So we're going to the Dog
Mountain Stratum to find a fool.
A transfer circle should
more than get the job done.
Two days later, our group arrived
at the Dog Mountain Stratum.
The name probably gave it away, but this
stratum has a giant dog-shaped rock.
Decay rock aside, it's a marine
stratum with tiny islands.
I hope we can spare some time for
a little fishing while we're here.
Captain Carry Oil does love to cast a rod.
I'd love to start doling out some
Hawaiian shirts and get the party started.
But we're not on vacation.
Oh, hey! Nice to meet you!
Fresh from a transfer circle?
Yep, we're here from the
Clear Flow Lake Stratum.
You are? That's great!
I've got to go tell the
director, so don't move an inch.
Are you folks really from another stratum?
You bet, mister.
Thank goodness the transfer
circles are finally working.
Now we can eat something other
than seafood for a change.
Did the monsters cause
any extra damage here?
Nah, we were plagued with frequent
monster attacks for a while there.
But then some incredible
hunters arrived and saved us.
Fortunately, that happened right before
the transfer circles stopped functioning.
So we made it through.
If you don't mind me asking,
did those hunters call themselves
the Menagerie of Fools?
Oh, so you know them.
Small world, eh?
Well, that's not good, but it's
probably okay, right? It's fine.
In fact, they contacted us earlier.
But regardless,
I highly doubt the director and the
others were able to convince her.
Hello, hello!
Thanks for visiting!
Make yourselves at home!
That looks like a kid, but I
guess it's the Stratum's director?
Oh, hello there!
It's been a while.
Yes, it most certainly has.
I'm the director of the Dog Mountain
Stratum's Hunters Association.
I brought you a letter
from Director Bear if you'd
like to take a look is
that a fact let me see oh.
This explains why the monsters
got so aggressive that's good
to know well good luck taking
care of all that weirdness.
You can let me know
when the job's finished?
Where do you think you're going?
Sorry, please forgive his rudeness.
He's basically the babysitter
if I'm understanding
the situation You need us
to help you find someone?
That's no problem whatsoever.
Can you describe them?
We greatly appreciate it.
I'll give you all the information we have.
While Heavy gave them the rundown, we
got to enjoy some primo relaxation.
How should we pass the time, Boxo?
I can't exactly go swimming.
The next best thing for a beach
day is to enjoy some fishing.
Tss, eef ood. Hmm?
Even my perceptive llamas
couldn't decipher that one.
It's tough not being able to talk.
I'll try again.
Cast-tat-la-tin. Hmm.
Si-i-foo-n.
Cast-tat-la-in?
You're saying you want to go fishing.
Yes, yes.
Llamas is out of this world.
I wasn't sure that was going to work.
I did it.
I knew I could figure it out.
All that's left is to
work out the details.
Yeah!
I really only know how
to do punchy fishing.
in a river that's technically not fishing
i love punchy fishing you can count me in!
but instead of using our
fists or nailing them
with rocks why don't we
try the laid back method?
for a change sounds fun!
great now we just need
the right equipment.
look no further ladies your friendly
neighborhood voxos got you covered.
doesn't look like you
have any rods for sale?
But we can probably
just use a stick. I see.
Some bags have pictures of fishing
lines with floats and hooks attached.
But some only have symbols on them.
Are those baits?
Hello there.
I'll go find some nice sticks for us.
Great.
Almost time for the moment of truth.
A lot of girls scream
and cry and yell, Ew,
that's grody, when they see
bait for the first time.
I'm weirdly fascinated to
see how those two will react.
Their cute expressions will be priceless.
I'm going to record it.
for science.
I've seen things like that, but a
little different at the river before.
This is kid stuff compared to some
of the monsters I've come across.
Yeah, I guess that tracks.
Why did I expect them to
freak out over a little
worm when they fight ugly
monsters on the regular?
Let's make this a tad more interesting.
Whoever catches the biggest one
will be named the fishing champ.
I'm not going to hold back!
Hello there.
I got one! Up you go!
Heck yeah, I got a shiwami!
I'm not gonna let you beat me! I-I win!
I'll let Hulemy take the prize,
but second place is mine!
Gotcha!
It'll break!
Grab the line, not the rod! Okay!
You hooked a fish monster! Reel it in!
I hear those things are delicious.
Look what I caught!
So she really caught a monster?
Huh?
Wait, did my hook snag on something?
The line might break if I pull any
harder, but this could be the big one.
I'm gonna go for it.
Oh, did you get a bite too, Boxo?
Hello there.
Need some help?
Yes, please.
I've got you covered.
That is one enormous clam.
I've never seen a monster
that looks like that.
Maybe it's a mutation?
You think it's tasty?
There's no telling.
But I'm curious, so let's cook it up.
This beast is looking good.
Master Boxo, I've been
searching high and low.
What are you doing out here?
Wow, that's a nice fish.
Oh, is that thing a clam?
Big clam.
It even took me shwell by surprise.
Huh, now I'm extra curious
to see what's inside.
Way too good.
You should have some too, Mishuel.
Don't mind if I do.
If Shui were here, she'd
probably eat it all herself.
Is that a challenge?
I'm going to need you to wipe
that greedy look off your face.
Everyone's here.
Now we can get the
seaside barbecue started.
Is that... No way. What the?
They're both looking at
that clam like they know it.
Shui, do you recognize that creature?
Sure do, I thought the same thing.
What else could it be?
Wait, what?
Is that some kind of monster?
Uh, so what was that about?
I beg your pardon.
That clam looked rather familiar.
It's so hot. Yikes.
That's not how you should
be treating poor pity.
A harmless shut-in.
I don't know.
Thank you
so
much for watching.
I look forward to serving you again.